## **ESTHER CAUVEN**

Wooloowin, QLD 4030 | ecauven@gmail.com | 0401167654 | linkedin.com/in/esthercauven

## **COMMUNICATIONS ASSISTANT**

Self-motivated, well-organised, and creative professional bringing excellent marketing and administration experience. I have exemplary multitasking abilities and proven organisational and customer relations skills. I am commended for solving problems and keeping on task to handle diverse business requirements. Through my versatile experience I have grown accustomed to balancing high-volume inquiries while prioritising tasks and optimising workflow. My passion lies in growing meaningful and authentic relationships and helping both my customers and organisation achieve their goals.

## **AREAS OF SKILL**

- Fluent in Dutch and English
- High level of proficiency in Spanish, Mandarin, and German
- Bachelor's Degree in Communication
- Highly proficient in SharePoint and Office365
- Good understanding of SEO

- Strong attention to detail
- Digital content generation
- Time management
- Organisation, prioritising, and multi-tasking
- Verbal and written communication
- Exceptionally fast learner
- Marketing strategy

**PROFESSIONAL HISTORY** 

Waitress 10/2020 to Current Reef Seafood and Sushi Newstead, QLD

My most recent role at Reef Seafood and Sushi was primarily in the customer service team where I maintained order efficiency and accuracy through clear communication with kitchen staff, earning numerous recommendations from satisfied customers. I often resolved customer complaints to maintain complete customer satisfaction. I was also responsible for collecting credit card, cash, and gift certificate payments and promptly answering customer telephone calls to avoid on-hold wait times. I could manage over 30 calls a shift, even during busy lunch or dinner times. Due to this fast-paced environment, I mastered the art of time management, while keeping a cool head, as I often had to juggle many tasks at once.

Marketing Administrator 04/2020 to 09/2020 The Solution Collective (SOCO) Brisbane, QLD

Previously I was employed by a niche SharePoint systems integrator called The Solution Collective (now: SOCO). I joined the team with the responsibility to drive significant change within the organisation, with a specific focus around determining and executing the organisation's marketing strategy.

## As part of this role, I:

- Designed and presented social media campaign ideas
- Wrote content
- Tracked key metrics and developed spreadsheets and data models
- Formulated customer case studies, and
- Worked closely with all product development departments to create and maintain marketing materials for sales presentations and client meetings.

When the organisation was in the middle of a rebranding stage, I was tasked with modernising web pages and social media presence as part of comprehensive strategies to enhance customer engagement. Due to the nature of the organisation, I was the "go-to" person in the office and I often completed administration-based tasks on top of my marketing responsibilities, such as supporting the sales team by coordinating paperwork and responding to basic inquiries. I maintained a complete database of all files and contacts and managed an efficient workflow between staff by effectively coordinating documents and communication.

Barista 11/2019 to 03/2020 Emjays Coffee Brisbane, QLD

As a barista, it was my responsibility to make up to 350 café beverages per day with speed, quality, and consistency. Especially during peak hour, I controlled the line and crowd with quick and efficient service, while remembering loyal customer's name and their usual order. I created original artwork for special board display daily, constantly expanded my personal knowledge of coffee styles and varieties, and elevated customer loyalty by using strong communication and problem solving abilities to resolve customer

**EDUCATION** 

**Bachelor's Degree** Oriental Languages and Communication, 07/2017 **Zuyd University of Applied Sciences** Maastricht, the Netherlands

Major in Chinese Language and Communication

Nankai University Tianjin, China, 01/2016

• Completed a semester of Chinese Language and Culture in China as part of my curriculum in the Netherlands.

**REFERENCES** 

**Antonio Liviani** Sales Manager, The Solution Collective (SOCO) antonioliviani@gmail.com

**Karina Hurman** Account Manager, Cisco khurman@cisco.com